

SOURAV HALDAR GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER

SUMMARY

Experienced Graphic Designer excited to focus on overseeing projects from concept through final delivery. Successfully creates brand messages, strategies and key graphic productions. Resourceful and hardworking with vendor sourcing expertise and empowering leadership skills illustrated over 3 years of industry success.

JOB EXPERIENCE_

2020 - Present

Graphics Designer & Web Developer

Digiedia

- Work closely with the director, copywriters, and other members of the marketing team to continuously level up the brand and develop new products
- Worked with editorial, product marketing, social, and creative teams to design marketing visual assets, which improved ad performance by 19%
- Designed and placed interactive flyers, ads, and banners on the site for upcoming promotions and events, increasing site visits by 40% for many Real Estate Companies, Educational Institutes, Hotel Chains, Clothing Stores etc.
- Designed the Launching poster of a bengali featured movie Pantua.
- Designed, Developed and Managed 20+ web design projects from start to finish using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and JQuery with 100% client satisfaction

2018 - Present

Freelancing

- I have been working with Tokyo Design Studio. A German based company and creating Social Media Posts for their products.
- I worked with taroob.in a Clothing Chain in editing their model's pictures & changing the backgrounds according to requirements.

2016

Frontend Development Training(Web Tech)

Mindtree Ltd.

- Had hands-on experience on Frontend Development using Bootstrap, Css , LESS , SASS and javascript.
- Learned to create High quality Layout for websites Using Tools and built them using Html.

SKILLS

Photoshop	• • • • •	After Effects	•••••
Illustrator	••••	Adobe XD	••••
Indesign	••••	Html	••••
Wordpress	• • • • • •	Javascript	••••

CONTACT_

• Narendra Nath Nandi Road, Madhyamgram, Kolkata_130

+91 78381 97973

souravhaldar2@amail.com

EDUCATION

Advance Graphics Designing

TGC India Pvt. Ltd 2017-2019

Bachelor Of Technology(ECE)

GGSIPU 2010-2015

Raisina Bengali School

Higher Secondary (CBSE) 2010

INTERESTS_

- TravellingHiking
- Sketching
- Bike Riding